VICTOR HUGO TERRA FORMISANO

E-mail victorformisano@gmail.com Phone Number +55 16 98813-3031

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/victor-formisano/ Portfolio

OBJECTIVES

To work as a full-stackweb developer and create highly complex websites and APIs. Perform maintenance tasks, automate processes, establish and maintain coding pattern and business rules. Additionally, contribute to the development team with technical expertise as well as soft skills such as communication, collaboration, and problem-solving.

MAIN STACKS LANGUAGES

Node.js, Next.js, React.js, MySQL, Git, SASS, Python, MySQL, MongoDB

- - Fluent Portuguese

Advanced English

WORK EXPERIENCE

Reduza Veículos – Ribeirão Preto

I worked as a systems developer and developed a website where I reached 50,000 monthly impressions with GoogleAds. I was able to develop my skills with **Django**, **FastAPI**, **React and MySQL**. In this way, it was possible to impact and capture new customers.

01/2022 - 07/2022 Outbound technical leader

Dryve - Ribeirão Preto

After demonstrating a strong commitment and hard work, I was promoted to Technical Lead in Customer Acquisition department with the goal of reducing customer acquisition costs. I had the opportunity to manage a team of 3 people and another things, I developed an API with Express.js that reduced lead generation costs by 20%.

Inside sales analyst

Dryve - Ribeirão Preto

I was hired to work in inside sales at Dryve, a company with an annual revenue of over 70 million dollars. I identified and improved processes using programming. Then I developed some task automation models with **Node.js and Python**, contributing to the creation of dashboards for insights in the area.

VOLUNTEER ROLE

Junior FEARP - Ribeirão Preto

I worked as a volunteer at Júnior FEARP, creating business plans for new companies in the region of the state of São Paulo. I was responsible for developing the statistical and financial indicators of some projects using **Python, SQL and Node.js.**

09/2020 - 11/2020 **Member**

Financial Market Club – Ribeirão Preto

I participated in the Financial Market Club, a university student league related to the investment market, where I had my first contact with programming, I developed portfolios of investment portfolios using **Python, HTML and CSS**. This experience allowed me to learn to manipulate data and create web projects and encouraged me to learn other important technologies for future projects.

EDUCATION

01/2020 - 12/2024 Bachelor's degree in Administration and Business.

School of Economics, Business Administration and Accounting University of São Paulo